<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PlantEEEi</string>
    <string name="home_home">Home</string>
    <string name="home_about">About</string>
    <string name="home_list">Plant List</string>


    <!-- <Add Plant Section> -->
    <string name="addplant_eggplant">Eggplant</string>
    <string name="addplant_eggplant_mini_desc">
        <p>Commonly used as a vegetable in dishes, but is, scientifically, actually, a fruit. The plant
            is one of the many vegetables you can grow in your garden, however, it is <b> very sensitive
                to cold</b>. Raw eggplant is composed of 92% water, 6% carbs, and 1% protein. </p>
    </string>
    <string name="addplant_kamote">Sweet Potato</string>
    <string name="addplant_kamote_mini_desc">
        <p>
             A root vegetable grown in tropical and subtropical regions worldwide that contains various Vitamins and Minerals, making it the second most important root crop grown globally (after cassava).
        </p>
    </string>

    <string name="addplant_soon">Plants Coming Soon !</string>
    <!-- </Add Plant Section> -->


    <!-- <Materials Section> -->
    <!--Sweet Potato-->
    <string name="mats_kamote_name"><b>Name:</b> \n\tSweet Potato</string>
    <string name="mats_kamote_sname"><b>Scientific Name:</b> \n\tIpomoea batatas</string>
    <string name="mats_kamote_weeks"><b>Weeks to grow:</b> \n\t18-27 weeks</string>
    <string name="mats_kamote_desc">
        The sweet potato is a dicotyledonous plant that belongs to the bindweed or morning glory family, Convolvulaceae. Its large, starchy, sweet-tasting, tuberous roots are a root vegetable.
Throughout Asia, people process sweet potato for snacks such as chips or animal feeds. Its tubers contain carbohydrates, protein, sodium), Vitamin A, Vitamin C, and calcium. Sweet potato is rich in dietary fiber, calcium, complex carbohydrates, and antioxidants.

    </string>
    <string name="kamote_mats_1">Mature sweet potato</string>
    <string name="kamote_mats_2">Container (jar)</string>
    <string name="kamote_mats_3">Shallow bowl</string>
    <string name="kamote_mats_4">Spading fork</string>
    <string name="kamote_mats_5">Watering can</string>


    <!--EggPlant-->
    <string name="mats_eggplant_name"><b>Name:</b> \n\tEggplant</string>
    <string name="mats_eggplant_sname"><b>Scientific Name:</b> \n\tSolanum melongena</string>
    <string name="mats_eggplant_weeks"><b>Weeks to grow:</b> \n\t16-24 weeks</string>
    <string name="mats_eggplant_desc">
        <p> The fruit is widely used in cooking. As a member of the genus Solanum,
            it is related to the tomato and the potato. Eggplant is one of the many vegetables
                you can grow in your garden, but the plant is very sensitive to cold.
                    Raw eggplant is composed of 92% water, 6% carbohydrates, 1% protein, and
                        negligible fat.</p>
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_mats_1">Small pots or trays</string>
    <string name="eggplant_mats_2">Large pot for mature eggplant (20 Liter capacity at least, preferably clay pot)</string>
    <string name="eggplant_mats_3">Potting soil</string>
    <string name="eggplant_mats_4">Sand</string>
    <string name="eggplant_mats_5">5-10-5 fertilizer</string>
    <string name="eggplant_mats_6">Wooden Support System</string>
    <string name="eggplant_mats_7">Gardening Trowel</string>
    <!-- </Materials Section> -->


    <!-- <Plant Steps> -->
    <!-- Sweet Potato -->
    <string name="kamote_steps_1">
        Growing your slips (Day 0)
        \n\t1. Clean the sweet potato and split it in half (or large sections).
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_2">
        \t2. Put them in a container with half of the potato submerged in water.
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_3">
        \t3. Put it in a window ledge or anywhere warm (e.g. on top of a radiator).
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_4">
        \t4. Observe if the slips are 6-9 inches long everyday within the first 6 weeks of planting.
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_5">\t5. Twist the slips off from the potato</string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_6">
        \t6. Transfer the slip to a shallow bowl with half the stem submerged in water.
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_7">
        \t7. Observe if the roots have grown about an inch and keep the water fresh (few days).
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_8">
        Transferring the Slips
        \n\t8. Make sure the soil is loose
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_9">
        \t9. Using a small hand trowel, dig a hole about 4" or 5" deep and 3" wide. Place one slip in each hole with the roots pointing down. Position the slip so that the bottom halfwill be covered with dirt while the top half with all of the new leaves is above ground.
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_10">
        \t10. Carefully cover the hole with soil and gently press (to remove remaining air pockets).
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_11">
        Growing the potatoes
        \n\t11. Water until the surrounding dirt is wet. Stop watering before your mound starts
                to erode.
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_12">\t12. Water everyday (first week after planting).</string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_13">\t13. Water every other day(second week).</string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_14">\t14. Water twice a week(third week).</string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_15">\t15. Water at least once a week (70-150 days).</string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_16">
        \t16. Check the soil everyday. Water the soil if it is dry.
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_17">
        Harvesting
        \n\t17. Observe if leaves start to yellow(everyday).
    </string>
    <string name="kamote_steps_18">
        \t18. Use a spading fork to dig tubers on a sunny day when the soil is dry.
    </string>


    <!-- Eggplant -->
    <string name="eggplant_steps_1">1. Clean your containers.</string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_2">
        2. Prepare soil. Mix 2 parts potting soil, 1 part sand.
                Mix a little compost and 5-10-5 fertilizer.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_3">3. Make a support system.</string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_4">
        4. Start indoors, temperature must be 12.8 C or higher. Fill your small pots or
                trays with the potting mix.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_5">
        5. Poke a ½ inch (1.25 cm) hole in the center of each pot or tray. Place 2
                seeds in each hole. Cover them afterwards, just lightly drop the soil
                    over the seeds, don’t pack it in.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_6">
        6. Set the pots or trays out on a warm, sunny windowsill. Ensure that the window
                receives at least 8 hours of sunlight a day.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_7">
        7. Water the seeds every day. Don’t create puddles of water on top of your soil but
                prevent the soil from drying out.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_8">
        8. Once the seedlings sprout two sets of leaves, snip out the weaker seedling, do not
                yank the weaker seedling out.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_9">
        9. Prepare for transplanting once the plant reaches at least ½ foot (15.25 cm) in height.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_10">
        10. Set up the supporting stakes in the permanent pot.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_11">
        11. Fill the permanent pot with the potting medium
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_12">
        12. Dig a hole in the center of the pot that is as deep and wide as the container the
                seedlings are currently planted in.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_13">
        13. Remove the seedling from its container and place it into the new pot. It is easier to
                transplant a wet and compact soil than dry, crumbly soil.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_14">14. Place the pot in a sunny location.</string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_15">
        15. Water the plant daily. You might need to water additionally if the weather
                is hot and dry
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_16">
        16. Add liquid fertilizer once every 2 weeks. Make sure you add fertilizer after watering
            the soil, don’t add fertilizer on dry soil.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_17">
        17. Tie the eggplant to the support to promote upward growth.
    </string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_18">18. Watch out for pests.</string>
    <string name="eggplant_steps_19">19. Harvest when the skin looks glossy.</string>
    <!-- </Plant Steps> -->


    <!-- About -->
    <string name="textView_app_about">
        \t<b>PlantEEEI</b> is an app that would assist its users, especially beginners, in planting. It would provide information on a number of species of plants and steps on taking care of the said species of plants among other things.

        \n\n\tThe app aims to encourage people to plant and/or grow fruits and vegetables, which can be used for their own consumption, to promote a greener household environment and, also, possibly, a better state of physical and mental health.
    </string>

    <string name="action_delete_plant">Delete Plant</string>
    <string name="dev1">
        \t\tMichael Angelo Asuncion
        \n\n\t\tBackend Developer
    </string>
    <string name="dev2">
        \t\tSean Michael Calingasan
        \n\n\t\tBackend Developer
    </string>
    <string name="dev3">
        \t\tMariam Paul Misagal
        \n\n\t\tFrontend Developer
    </string>
    <string name="dev4">
        \t\tEyanne Kyle Ranjo
        \n\n\t\tFrontend Developer
    </string>
    <string name="about_dev">
        \tThe Developer team consists of four members, all currently taking BS Computer Engineering as their degree program in the University of the Philippines-Diliman.
    </string>
    <string name="app_version">
        PlantEEEi Version 1.0
        \n\u00A9 All Rights Reserved 2018
    </string>



    <!-- Used for PlantStats Action Bar -->

    <string name="title_activity_materials">Materials</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">test</string>
    <string name="title_activity_plant_stats">Plant Stats</string>
    <string name="title_activity_addplant">Add Plant</string>
    <string name="title_activity_plant_steps">Plant Steps</string>


</resources>
